(Amy:)Well, as long as we're
suspending the parameters,
(Amy:)I could stay really late
(Amy:)and we could have
our first sleepover.
(Sheldon:)That's a big step.
(Amy:)It's a big fort.
(Sheldon:)Very well.
(Sheldon:)I will agree
to a family-friendly,
(Sheldon:)G-rated, boy-girl sleepover.
(Amy:)PG.
(Amy:)Some scenes may be too intense
for younger viewers.
(Sheldon:)G-rated,
(Sheldon:)with a warning for families
with babies and toddlers.
(Amy:)You got yourself a sleepover.
(Sheldon:)Do you need to borrow
(Sheldon:)a toothbrush or pajamas?
(Amy:)Would it alarm you to know
(Amy:)that I hid those things here
two years ago
(Amy:)just in case this ever came up?
(Raj:)It would,
(Sheldon:)but you know how much
I admire preparedness.
(Sheldon:)How did you know we'd be
in the living room?